mgmresorts.com 2011-05-15

# MGM Resorts International Privacy Statement

## Revised: June 22, 2009

MGM Resorts International values your patronage and respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy ("Policy") describes the privacy practices of MGM Resorts International, the MGM Resorts International Web Sites, and the MGM Resorts International Resorts and Casinos described below (collectively, "us" or "we"), including how personal information about you may be obtained, used, and disclosed by us. This Policy also describes how you can opt-out of some uses of personal information. You may click _[here](http://www.mgmmirage.com/privacy_faq.htm)_ to view Frequently Asked Questions or _[here](http://www.mgmmirage.com/TermsOfUse.htm)_ to review the Terms of Use for MGM Resorts International Web Sites. If, after reviewing this Policy, you have any privacy questions or concerns, you may contact us at _[privacy@mgmresorts.com](mailto:privacy@mgmresorts.com)_. 

This Policy applies only to MGM Resorts International, the MGM Resorts International web sites that post this Policy (collectively, "MGM Resorts International Web Sites"), and the resorts, casinos and other MGM Resorts International properties listed below (collectively, "MGM Resorts International Resorts and Casinos"): 

ARIA Resort and Casino in Las Vegas, Nevada  
Beau Rivage in Biloxi, Mississippi   
Bellagio in Las Vegas, Nevada  
Circus Circus in Las Vegas, Nevada   
Circus Circus in Reno, Nevada  
CityCenter Residential Division in Las Vegas, Nevada  
Excalibur in Las Vegas, Nevada  
Gold Strike in Jean, Nevada  
Gold Strike Resort in Tunica, Mississippi  
Luxor in Las Vegas, Nevada  
Mandalay Bay in Las Vegas, Nevada  
MGM Grand in Las Vegas, Nevada  
MGM Grand Detroit in Detroit, Michigan   
Monte Carlo in Las Vegas, Nevada  
New York-New York in Las Vegas, Nevada  
Skylofts at MGM Grand in Las Vegas, Nevada  
The Crystals at CityCenter in Las Vegas, Nevada  
THEhotel at Mandalay Bay in Las Vegas, Nevada   
The Mirage in Las Vegas, Nevada   
The Signature at MGM Grand in Las Vegas, Nevada  
Vdara Condo Hotel at CityCenter in Las Vegas, Nevada

This Policy does not apply to any other web sites, including other web sites that may be owned, operated, or affiliated with MGM Resorts International or its subsidiaries. Nor does it apply to any other subsidiaries of MGM Resorts International, or to any other resorts, casinos, or other properties that are owned, operated, or affiliated with MGM Resorts International or its subsidiaries. 

## I .INFORMATION WE COLLECT

### A.Personal Information that You Provide Voluntarily to Us

"Personal Information" is information through which you can be identified. We collect Personal Information that you provide voluntarily to us through a variety of means. Some examples of Personal Information that we collect include your name, date of birth, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, gender, gaming activity, and purchase and reservation information. If you visit MGM Resorts International Resorts and Casinos, Personal Information may include your image in a live video feed that can be viewed on the MGM Resorts International Web Sites. Some Personal Information is considered "Confidential Personal Information." Confidential Personal Information is your name in combination with one or more of the following: credit or debit card number, financial account number, driver's license number, state identification card number, Social Security number, passport number, and naturalization number. 

### B. Personal Information that We Obtain From Partners

We may obtain Personal Information from carefully selected business partners including entities that direct you to, or are located at, MGM Resorts International Web Sites or MGM Resorts International Resorts and Casinos (collectively "Partners"). We may use Personal Information obtained from our Partners in accordance with the terms of this Policy. We generally have no control over how our Partners use Personal Information they collect from or about you. Therefore, if you provide Personal Information, including Confidential Personal Information, to our Partners, we encourage you to consult our Partners' privacy policies for more information about their privacy protection practices. 

### C. Personal Information Collected by Third Parties

Certain transactions and services offered while visiting MGM Resorts International Web Sites may be processed or provided by third parties under contract with us for fulfillment and other purposes. When your Personal Information is submitted to these third parties for such purposes, we require those third parties to exercise reasonable care to protect your Personal Information and restrict the use of your Personal Information to the purposes for which it was provided. 

### D. Non-Personal Information

"Non-Personal Information" is information about you or your activities through which you cannot be personally identified. When you use the Internet, your web browser or software may transmit certain information to the servers that host the web sites you visit. Such information may include, for example, the unique number assigned to your server or Internet connection, your geographic location, and your interactions with the MGM Resorts International Web Sites, including what pages you look at and what information you download. When you visit the MGM Resorts International Web Sites, our servers collect Non-Personal Information. In situations where it is possible to do so, Non-Personal Information may be linked to Personal Information. 

### E. Cookies

A cookie is a small file that contains information sent by a web site that is saved on your computer's hard drive. Cookies have become a standard feature of Internet commercial web sites. MGM Resorts International Web Sites use cookies to personalize your experience and to gather data such as which web pages you visit and what material you download. Cookies also are used to put a unique identifier on your computer. This helps us to generate statistics regarding usage of MGM Resorts International Web Sites, such as the percentage of repeat visitors. In situations where it is possible to do so, this unique identifier may be linked to Personal Information. You can prevent a cookie from being used on your computer. To browse the Internet and MGM Resorts International Web Sites without using cookies, you can configure your browser to reject all cookies or to notify you when each cookie is offered so that you can accept or reject each cookie. However, if you reject all cookies, you may not be able to conduct some transactions or use some services on MGM Resorts International Web Sites. 

## II. HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT 

### A. Uses by MGM Resorts International 

Except for Confidential Personal Information, we may use Personal Information and Non-Personal Information for our own marketing purposes, including notifying you of special promotions, offers and events via postal mail, e-mail, telephone, text message, and other means. Confidential Personal Information will not be used for our own marketing purposes without your express consent. 

We may also use Personal Information and Non-Personal Information for non-marketing purposes. Some examples of such use include (1) processing and fulfilling reservations or purchases; (2) conducting statistical or demographic analysis; (3) tracking reservations and corresponding hotel stays generated through our affiliate program and calculating or auditing commissions that may be paid in relation to a hotel stay; (4) customizing your experience at MGM Resorts International Web Sites; and (5) responding to your inquiries or other communications. 

We may combine Personal Information with other generally or publicly available information to help us identify your preferences or interests. Your Personal Information may also be merged with Personal Information available from other sources such as (1) companies that match e-mail addresses with postal addresses; (2) credit card verification and credit services; and (3) other resorts, casinos, or properties that are owned, operated, or affiliated with MGM Resorts International or its subsidiaries.

If you do not want us to use your Personal Information for marketing purposes, you may opt-out of such uses by notifying us in accordance with Section III.B. below. Opting-out will not prevent your Personal Information (including Confidential Personal Information) from being used for non-marketing purposes. 

### B. Sharing within MGM Resorts International and with Subsidiaries 

Except for Confidential Personal Information, your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information may be shared for any purpose (1) among MGM Resorts International, MGM Resorts International Resorts and Casinos and MGM Resorts International Web Sites, and (2) with MGM Resorts International subsidiaries not covered by this Policy, and any other resorts, casinos, or other properties that are owned, operated by or affiliated with MGM Resorts International or its subsidiaries (collectively, "Subsidiaries"). If you do not want your Personal Information to be shared among MGM Resorts International, MGM Resorts International Resorts and Casinos and MGM Resorts International Web Sites or with Subsidiaries for marketing purposes, you may opt-out of such sharing by notifying us in accordance with Section III.B. below. 

Although you may request to opt-out of sharing Personal Information for marketing purposes, we may share Personal Information among MGM Resorts International, MGM Resorts International Resorts and Casinos and MGM Resorts International Web Sites and with Subsidiaries for non-marketing purposes. Confidential Personal Information will only be shared among MGM Resorts International, MGM Resorts International Resorts and Casinos and MGM Resorts International Web Sites and with Subsidiaries to the extent necessary to permit validation of your identity, completion of a purchase or credit transaction, recording of gaming-related activity, or other legitimate non-marketing business purposes.

### C. Sharing With Partners for Marketing Purposes

Except for Confidential Personal Information, we may share your Personal Information with our Partners for joint marketing efforts, or for our Partners' own marketing purposes. When we provide Personal Information to our Partners, we require those Partners to exercise reasonable care to protect your Personal Information and restrict the use of your Personal Information to the purposes for which it was provided to them. To determine how Partners use the Personal Information they collect directly from you, or about you, from sources other than us, please consult the privacy policies of our Partners. If you do not want us to share your Personal Information with Partners for marketing purposes, you may opt-out of such sharing by notifying us in accordance with Section III.B. below. 

### D. Sharing With Partners and Other Third Parties for Non-Marketing Purposes 

Although you may request to opt-out of sharing Personal Information for marketing purposes, we may disclose Personal Information, including Confidential Personal Information, to our Partners and other third parties for the following purposes: 

(1) if you enroll in our Responsible Gaming Program (see "Responsible Gaming Program" in Section V below);   
(2) for non-marketing purposes, such as processing and fulfilling reservations or purchases;   
(3) in connection with a business transaction involving a sale, purchase, reorganization, or transfer to a third party of any of the assets of MGM Resorts International, any MGM Resorts International Resort and Casino, and/or any MGM Resorts International Web Site;   
(4) to comply with a court order, subpoena, search warrant or other valid legal process;   
(5) to comply with legal, regulatory or administrative requirements of any governmental authorities;   
(6) to protect and defend MGM Resorts International, its subsidiaries and affiliates, and all of their officers, directors, employees, attorneys and agents in connection with any legal action, claim or dispute;   
(7) to satisfy any contractual obligation to indemnify our contractors, Partners or other third parties in connection with any legal action, claim or dispute;   
(8) to enforce the Terms of Use of MGM Resorts International Web Sites;   
(9) to prevent imminent physical harm or threats to public safety;   
(10) to third-party vendors that MGM Resorts International may use to perform functions on behalf of MGM Resorts International, such as companies that process credit card transactions;   
(11) to prevent fraud; and   
(12) to engage in debt collection. 

When we provide Personal Information to our Partners and other third parties for such purposes, we require those Partners and third parties to exercise reasonable care to protect your Personal Information and restrict the use of your Personal Information to the purposes for which it was provided to them. 

## III. YOUR COMMUNICATION PREFERENCES 

### A. Establishing a Preference Account 

We are committed to protecting the accuracy and confidentiality of your Personal Information and encourage you to tell us how you want us to communicate with you and let you know about special offers. By creating an MGM Resorts International Preference Account, you can view and update your Personal Information and choose your communication preferences. Your Preference Account gives you the ability to choose which MGM Resorts International Resorts and Casinos and MGM Resorts International Web Sites you would like to receive communications from and how. You can select from communications preference options including direct mail, e-mail, telemarketing, and text messaging. To create a Preference Account or to update your preferences at any time after you have created your Preference Account, click [here](https://secure02.mgm-mirage.com/Guestbook/privacy.aspx) or visit any MGM Resorts International Web Site and select "E-mail Promotions" or "Guestbook". These options will allow you to create and access your Preference Account.

If you are a member of Players Club, you may update your communications preferences by visiting [www.mlife.com](https://www.mlife.com/), logging in to your account, and selecting "Update Account".

### B. How to Opt-Out 

If you wish to opt-out of receiving solicitations from us or do not want us to share your Personal Information with Partners for marketing purposes, you can record your preferences by clicking [here](https://secure02.mgm-mirage.com/Guestbook/privacy.aspx). To opt-out, you can also email us at [privacy@mgmresorts.com](mailto:privacy@mgmresorts.com), call (866) 761-7111, or write to:

MGM Resorts International   
Attn: Privacy Policy  
840 Grier Drive Suite 200   
Las Vegas, Nevada 89119 

If you do not want us to share your Personal Information among MGM Resorts International Resorts and Casinos and MGM Resorts International Web Sites or with Subsidiaries for marketing purposes, you may e-mail us at [privacy@mgmresorts.com](mailto:privacy@mgmresorts.com) or call (866) 761-7111.

### C. Telemarketing

Even if you registered your telephone number on a Do-Not-Call list, certain exemptions may allow us to contact you by telephone. However, to ensure our customers' preferences are honored, we also maintain our own internal do-not-call list. If you would like to opt-out of receiving telemarketing sales calls from us by adding your telephone number to our internal do-not-call list, please click [here](http://www.mgmresorts.com/dnc/). 

## IV. SECURITY 

Personal Information (including Confidential Personal Information) and Non-Personal Information collected by MGM Resorts International, the MGM Resorts International Web Sites and MGM Resorts International Resorts and Casinos are stored on secure servers. The secure servers are protected by firewalls and other industry standard security measures. These security measures are instituted to ensure the protection of these secure servers from unauthorized access. However, no security system is impenetrable, and these systems could become accessible in the event of a security breach. We have controls in place that are designed to detect potential data breaches, contain and minimize the loss of data, and conduct forensic investigations of a breach. 

Our staff is required to take reasonable measures to ensure that unauthorized persons cannot view or access your Personal Information. Employees who violate our privacy policies are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination.

We cannot enforce or control the security of the computers, electronic devices, or electronic communication method that a consumer may use to send e-mails and submit information to us over the Internet. You are responsible for ensuring that the computers, electronic devices and electronic communication methods you use will provide adequate security for communicating with us. We are not responsible for the disclosure or interception of your information before we receive it.

As a standard security practice, we will take reasonable steps which are standard in the industry to ensure that the communication methods used to support the MGM Resorts International Web Sites do not permit connection or communication by methods that have known security weaknesses or vulnerabilities. As such, if you experience trouble using an MGM Resorts International Web Site, it may be an indication that you need to upgrade your Internet browsing tool or application to a newer version that supports more secure communication methods. 

## V. RESPONSIBLE GAMING PROGRAM 

MGM Resorts International is a member of the American Gaming Association and adheres to its Code of Conduct for Responsible Gaming. Accordingly, we will not use the Personal Information of members of the MGM Resorts International Self-Limit Access Program of Nevada, Self-Exclusion Program of Mississippi, or Disassociated Persons Program of Michigan, as applicable, for any marketing purposes. 

## VI. OTHER WEB SITES 

We are not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices of other web sites, including web sites operated by our Partners. You should review and understand the privacy policies posted on any linked sites you visit before providing any Personal Information.

## VII. PERSONS UNDER AGES 18 AND 21 

Certain of our areas and activities are intended for persons 21 or older. If you are under 21, we ask that you do not access or attempt to access any areas or participate in any activities that are restricted to persons 21 or older. We do not knowingly collect or allow the collection of Personal Information from persons under 18. If you are the parent or guardian of a person under 18 and believe that the person has provided us with Personal Information, you may contact us at [privacy@mgmresorts.com](mailto:privacy@mgmresorts.com) and request that it be deleted from our files. We will delete the Personal Information of any person under 18 and will not use such Personal Information for any purpose.

## VIII. VISITORS OUTSIDE OF THE UNITED STATES 

The MGM Resorts International Web Sites are maintained on servers located in the United States, and Personal Information and Non-Personal Information are stored on computers and servers located in the United States. The United States may not offer a level of privacy protection for Personal Information (including Confidential Personal Information) as great as that offered in other jurisdictions. Therefore, the disclosure of Personal Information pursuant to this Policy is at your own risk. We make no representation that the practices described in this Policy are compliant with laws outside of the United States that apply to the collection, security, use and disclosure of Personal Information. 

## IX. CHANGES TO THIS POLICY 

We reserve the right to revise this Policy at any time without notice. When this Policy is revised in a material way, notice will be posted on the MGM Resorts International Web Sites along with the revised Policy.
